A Guide to the Vouchers for old treasury warrants from the Virginia Land Office, 1779-1783
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Vouchers for old treasury warrants from the Virginia Land Office, 1779-1783
The Library of Virginia
LOI 21
3.7 cu ft (11 boxes)
Virginia. Auditor of Public Accounts (1776-1928)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession LOI 21 transferred by the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1948.
Historical Information
The act which established the previous Land Office passed the General Assembly on 22 June 1779. The register was the head of the Office and was appointed by joint ballot of both houses of the legislature.
Scope and Content
These records contain printed vouchers, signed by the state auditors, on which warrants were issued. They contain the amount of money paid into the treasury by an individual and the number of acres to which this sum entitled him. The basis for the allowance, whether by the act establishing the Land Office or by any one of several special acts under which land was available, is also recorded. In several instances, later warrants were blended with earlier ones. Records cover the period from 1779 Oct 6 to 1783 Dec 24.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
VIrginia. Land Office.
Subjects:
Land grants -- Virginia -- 18th century.
Genre and Form Terms:
State government records -- Virginia; Vouchers
Contents List
- Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 1779-1783., Extent: 11 boxes. (Box 1-11)
  Chronological
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 1-3399, 1779-1780. (Box 1)
    - #1-299, October 1779. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - #300-649 October 1779. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - #650-1349 October 1779. (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Lacking warrants 1060, 1097, 1192, 1336
    - #1350-2450 October 1779-February 1780. (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Lacking warrants 1376-1377, 1431, 2032
    - #2451-2799 February 1780. (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Lacking warrant 2729
    - #2800-3399 February 1780-March 1780. (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Lacking warrant 3192
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 3400-6305, 1780-1781. (Box 2)
    - #3400-3950 March 1780. (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Lacking 3616
    - #4450-5199 March 1780. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - #4450-5199 March 1780-June 1780. (Box 2, Folder 3)
      4537, 4563, 4566, 4676, 5184
    - #5200-6305 June 1780-June 1781. (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Lacking 5825-5828, 6144, 6159-6161, 6234, 6284
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 6306-8999, 1781-1782. (Box 3)
    - #6306-7108 June 1781-October 1781. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - #7109-7899 October 1781-November 1781. (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Lacking warrant 7535
    - #7900-8399 November 1781-April 1782. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - #8400-8999 October 1781-April 1782. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 9000-11300 1781-1782. (Box 4)
    - #9000-9599 November 1781-December 1781. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - #9600-10274 December 1781. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - #10275-10899 December 1781-February 1782. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - #10900-11300 February 1782-March 1782. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 11301-12350 1782. (Box 5)
    - #11301-11599 March 1782. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Lacking warrant 11543
    - #11600-11850 March 1782-April 1782. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Lacking warrants 11727-11734
    - #11851-12100 April 1782-May 1782. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Lacking warrant 12052
    - #12101-12350 May 1782-June 1782. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 12351-14100 1782. (Box 6)
    - #12351-12699 June 1782. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - #12700-13025 May 1782-July 1782. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - #13026-13949 August 1782. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - #13950-14100 August 1782-September 1782. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 14101-14999 1782. (Box 7)
    - #14101-14350 September 1782. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - #14351-14550 September 1782. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - #14551-14899 September 1782-December 1782. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - #14900-14999 December 1782. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 15000-16650 1782-1783. (Box 8)
    - #15000-15125 December 1782-March 1783. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - #15126-15550 March 1783-April 1783. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - #15551-16600 April 1783-May 1783. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - #16601-16650 May 1783. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 16651-17125 1782. (Box 9)
    - #16651-17125 May 1783-June 1783. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - #17126-17449 June 1783. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - #17450-18218 June 1783-August 1783. (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Lacking warrants 17539-17540
    - #18219-18925 August 1783. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 18926-20299 1783. (Box 10)
    - #18926-19200 August 1783-September 1783. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - #19201-19460 September 1783. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - #19461-19900 September 1783-October 1783. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Lacking warrants 19605-19642, 19697, 19700-19702, 19826-19830
    - #19901-20299 October 1783-November 1783. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Old Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 20300-21226 1783-1784. (Box 11)
    - #20300-21226 November 1783. (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Lacking warrant 20864
    - #21227-23084 November 1783-June 1784. (Box 11, Folder 2)